A Guide to the YMCA of Greater Richmond Records, 1854-2019 (bulk 1920-1998)
Library of Virginia
- Series VI: YMCA Library, 7 cu. ft.
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1974 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1975 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1976 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1977 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1978 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1979 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1980 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1981 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1982 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1983 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1984 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1985 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1986 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1987 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1988 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1989 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1990 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1992 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1993 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1994 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1997 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 1999 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 2000 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 2001 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 2002 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA Year Book and Official Roster and Directory, 2003 (Volume On shelf)
  - Balhuizen, Anne Ross, "Searching on Location: Planning a Research Trip," 1992 (Volume On shelf)
  - "Christadelphian Ecclesia," nd (Volume On shelf)
  - "Crews, Edward R., "The Richmond YMCA 1854-2004," 2004 (Volume On shelf)
  - "Discovering the YMCA," 1984 (Volume On shelf)
  - Doggett, L.L., "Life of Robert R. McBurney," 1925 (Volume On shelf)
  - Freeman, Douglas Southall, "When War Came to Richmond," 1981 (Volume On shelf)
  - Glassner, Gregory Kurt, "Extra Billy Smith: Virginia's Governor/General," 2000 (Volume On shelf)
  - Griffin, James and Tim Lomas, "Exploring Local History," 2004 (Volume On shelf)
  - Hall, Mary Ross and Helen Firman Sweet, "Women in the YMCA Record," 1947 (Volume On shelf)
  - Hinding, Andrea, "Proud Heritage: A History of Pictures of the YMCA in the United States," 1988 (Volume On shelf)
  - Lancaster, Richard C., "Serving the U.S. Armed Forces 1861-1986: The Story of the YMCA's Ministry to Military Personnel for 125 Years," 1987 (Volume On shelf)
  - Latourette, Kenneth Scott, "World Service: A history of the foreign work and world service of the Young Men's Christian Associations of the United States and Canada," 1957 (Volume On shelf)
  - Mathews, Basil, "John R. Mott: World Citizen," 1934 (Volume On shelf)
  - Moore, John F., "The Story of the Railroad "Y"," 1930 (Volume On shelf)
  - Pence, Owen E., "The Y.M.C.A. and Social Need," 1946 (Volume On shelf)
  - Pierrel Gren O., ed., "The Executive role in Y.M.C.A. Administration...An Analysis and Discussion of the Administrative Processes in the North American Y.M.C.A.'s," 1951 (Volume On shelf)
  - Richmond Times Dispatch, "Famous Front Pages," 2000 (Volume On shelf)
  - Robert, General Henry M., "Robert's Rules of Order Revised," 1943 (Volume On shelf)
  - "St. Paul's Episcopal Church: 150 Years 1845-1995," 1995 (Volume On shelf)
  - "Service with Fighting Men: An Account of the Work of the American Young Men's Christian Association in the World War," 1922 (Volume On shelf)
  - Simpson, Lewis P., "Mind and the American Civil War," 1989 (Volume On shelf)
  - Sowchek, Ellen, "One Hundred Years in Retrospect: A Highly Personal Look at YMCA History," 1978 (Volume On shelf)
  - "Songs of Faith," 1933 (Volume On shelf)
  - Tyler, Lyon Gardiner, "A Confederate Catechism: The War for Southern Self Government," 1935 (Volume On shelf)
  - Vandiver, Frank E., "1001 Things Everyone Should Know About the Civil War," 1999 (Volume On shelf)
  - Varhola, Michael J., "Everday life during the Civil War: A guide for writers, students, and historians," 1999 (Volume On shelf)
  - Williams, J.E. Hodder, "The Life of Sir George Williams Founder of the Young Men's Christian Association," 1906 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA, "The Jubilee of Work for Young Men in North America," 1901 (Volume On shelf)
  - YMCA, "YMCA in America 1851-2001," 2001 (Volume On shelf)
- Series VII: Artifacts, 1979-2000, 1 cu. ft. (1 box); Box 63. (Box 63)